[{"answer": "Look, we're focused on getting the delegates we need to get the nomination.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Are you a bit mystified that people aren't really galvanized yet into Mitt Romney being the nominee?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, we always knew that this would be a long fight.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Is that really helpful to either Mitt Romney or to the party itself?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, at first we challenge the statement that he's not a true conservative.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "I mean how far do you take on Rick Santorum in that kind of territory?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "You know, I think just getting his message out is the most important thing.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What do you think have been the main things that he's learned so far on this campaign trail?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "You know, that's going to be up to all the individual campaigns, and I'll let their campaigns decide that.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "I mean, do you think it's time that one of the contestants, maybe more than one, consider whether to pull out?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there's a couple of things that the Romney people, for some reason, always seem to fail to tell anybody and that is that many of the delegates that are already there are not binding delegates.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "How are you actually going to win this?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Well, look, Newt Gingrich is going to have to do what Newt Gingrich has to do.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Could you see Newt Gingrich doing that?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the interesting thing, I will say this, this probably the first campaign in the history of political -- of presidential politics in recent history that we do not have a pollsters, we do not have wordsmiths always telling the candidate what to do.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "And finally, John, and briefly if you don't mind, can we assume that we will not be seeing Rick Santorum uttering the word snob again in this campaign, or actually college education, and that he will desist from saying John F. Kennedy made him throw up?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let me say, I am not going to see \"Game Change.\"", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What was your memory of the whole process?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "It is day by day.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What goes through the mind of a wife in this situation?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "It is great.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Well, the prize is so great, isn't it?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, let's step back just a little bit.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "But do you think it is time that one or two of the candidates pulled out?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "I mean did you think that he was being bigoted, Kirk Cameron?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "CCAIN: It is too harsh.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Is it too harsh to say that?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I -- I am -- I'm strongly -- I strongly disagree.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "And what did you think of Rush Limbaugh's comments?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Yes, I know.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "But that's the sense that came through, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Should someone like him be on air after saying something so offensive?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, it's a very interesting video clip.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "What do you think of this video clip?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Law school.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Who cares?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "It's an indictment of Ben.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Why didn't we see it in 2007 or 2008?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I have to correct Ben real quick, because we actually had the footage.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "What's your view of all this?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I am just worried about it becoming a distraction.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Is it a valid thing to whack the president with or is it a lot of hot air about nothing, do you think?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I think it's not a question of if.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "It would seem, from an outsider, that Romney is going to walk this, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I don't know if there's the moment, but they certainly don't want it to go all the way up to the convention.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "They've got to work out the moment when they are going to press the button on the nominee, haven't they?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "He seems to be -- I agree with Amy.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Or does the constant mudslinging by his competitors now in his party kill the brand a bit?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "July.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Let me start with you, Carol?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "The month when it is exactly right.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Amy?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "July probably.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Dana?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I think they'll lock it up in May, maybe confirm it in June.", "docId": "120307pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Ben?", "qSentId": 671}]